Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, Chancellor, Records, 1970 - 1985
Duke University. University Archives
- Subject Files, 1970-1985 and undated.
  - Publications, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Pye, A. Kenneth, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - R, General, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Racquet Club, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Real Estate, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Registrar, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Religion, Department of, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Research Support, Office of, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Unfunded Professorships, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - RTI Board of Governors (3 folders), 1981-1984 (Box 18)
  - Retirement, 1982 July-1985 (Box 18)
  - Rochester, University of: Financial Analysis, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Romance Languages, Department of, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - ROTC: Air Force, 1982 July-1984 (Box 19)
  - Aerospace Studies, 1981 July-1983 (Box 19)
  - ROTC: Army, 1982 July-1985 (Box 19)
  - ROTC: Navy, 1982 July-1985 (Box 19)
  - Russian Exchange Program, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Public Safety, Office of, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - S, General, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sanford Recognition Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sanford, President Terry, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Scholarships: Four-County Scholarship Program, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Search Committees: Other Universities, 1983-1985 (Box 19)
  - Campus Security, 1983-1984 (Box 19)
  - Semans, Mary Duke Biddle Trent, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sexual Harassment (2 folders), 1982 July-1984 (Box 19)
  - Shrivastav, Mrs. Shashi, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Shell Foundation, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Skarulis, Mrs. Patricia, 1983-1985 (Box 19)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Smithsonian (Radiation Biology Laboratory), 1982 (Box 19)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1982 July-1985 (Box 19)
  - Segregated Facilities, University Policy on, 1976-1980 (Box 19)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly, 1982 July-1984 (Box 19)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1982-1984 (Box 19)
  - SECID (South-East Consortium for International Development), 1982 (Box 19)
  - Special Events, Office of, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Speech Material, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Speech Writer: Applicants, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Speech Writers, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Statement of Intent, 1982-1984 (Box 19)
  - Statistics and Decision Sciences, Center for, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Steam Plant, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Stubbing, Richard, 1981-1985 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs, Office of, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Student Health, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Study Abroad Program, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
  - Summer Transitional Program, 1982 (Box 20)
  - T, General, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Talent Identification Program: Robert Sawyer, Director, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Technical Support Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 20)
  - Tel-Com, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Local Area Network Communications Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Temporary Services, 1982-1984 (Box 20)
  - Ten Universities Group, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Third World Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - TIAA-CREF, 1982 July-1985 (Box 20)
  - Traffic and Parking, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Translation Service, undated (Box 20)
  - Trent Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
  - Triangle Universities Center for Advance Studies (2 folders), 1980-1985 (Box 20)
  - Triangle Universities Computation Center (2 folders), 1980-1985 (Box 20)
  - Tuition Assistance for Employees, 1983-1985 (Box 20)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Turnover Reports, undated (Box 20)
  - U, General, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts and Sciences, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Advisory Group, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - University Marshall, 1983 (Box 21)
  - University Relations, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Research Council, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Technology Corporation (UTC), 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Union, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - U. S. Department of Education, 1984 (Box 21)
  - V, General, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Visitors Center, 1982 (Box 21)
  - W, General, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - WDBS, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Wage and Salary, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Ward, James A. (University Architect), 1982 July (Box 21)
  - White House Conference on Productivity, 1983 (Box 21)
  - White, Professor Richard (Dean of Arts & Sciences and Trinity College), 1985 (Box 21)
  - Women Faculty, Committee on, 1982-1984 (Box 21)
  - Women of Achievement, 1983-1985 (Box 21)
  - Women's Studies Research Center, 1982-1984 (Box 21)
  - Y, General, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Zoology, Department of, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Stepan, Alfred (Yale University), 1983 (Box 21)
  - Genetics Site Visit, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center: Dr. William G. Anlyan, 1982-1985 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Advisory Board, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - Community and Family Medicine, Department of, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center: Community Health Services, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Center for Health Policy Research and Education (CHPRE) (3 folders), 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Development, 1982-1985 (Box 22)
  - Employee and Staff Health Facilities (Pickens, etc.) 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - Health Administration, Department of, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center: Highland Hospital, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Durham County General Hospital, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Hospital Budget, 1982-1985 (Box 22)
  - Howard Hughes Lab Building, 1982-1985 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Marriott: Servicemaster, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center: Duke Hospital North, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center: School of Nursing, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - Medical Center Overview Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 23)
  - Medical Center PDC, 1982-1984 (Box 23)
  - You, Dr. Kwah-sa, Department of Pediatrics, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Medical Center Private Sector, 1983-1985 (Box 23)
  - Putnam, Dr. Charles, 1982-1985 (Box 23)
  - Medical Center Satellite Clinic, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Medical Center: Sea Level Hospital, 1982-1985 (Box 23)
  - Spicer, Dr. Leonard (2 folders), 1982-1985 (Box 23)
  - Toxicology, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Wadsworth Dedication (Eye Center), 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Medical Center: Whitehead Endowment, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Dr. Andrew, 1982-1983 (Box 23)
  - Yaggy, Dr. Duncan, 1982-1985 (Box 23)
  - Interim Report: Advisory Group to DUMC, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Restricted Materials
    RESTRICTED: The following folders contain materials of a sensitive nature and are restricted. It should not be assumed, however, that the rest of the collection is unrestricted, as this collection is unprocessed and may contain other sensitive materials.
    - Ferrer v. Duke University (3 folders), 1982-1984 (Box 23)
    - Opportunity Development Center (2 folders), 1982-1985 (Box 23)
    - O'Brien, Matthew P., 1983-1984 (Box 23)
    - Roberts, Allen, 1984 (Box 23)
    - Tenure Cases, 1984 (Box 23)
Related Material
H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963-1994
Duke University Archives
Oral history interview with H. Keith H. Brodie, 2004
Duke University Medical Center Library
H. Keith H. Brodie and Leslie Banner
The Research University Presidency in the Late Twentieth Century: A Life Cycle/Case History Approach. Westport, Conn.: Praeger Publishers, 12005
H. Keith H. Brodie and Leslie Banner
Keeping an Open Door: Passages in a University Presidency. Durham, NC: Duke University Press, 1996